Okay, so now what we're going to do right here is we're going to add the lamp or you
can say our light where the objectives will be or where there will be some pickable items
okay.
If you want you can skip this video but if you want to add this functionality then follow
me step by step.
Okay, make sure that you download the zip file and let me tell you that this lamp is from
this sketch for this 3D available right here this is the creator name all right so if you
want you can go ahead and download it from here and also you can give a like to the creator
for this purple color right so the reason I'm telling you to download this zip is because
in this I have fixed the materials and also I've added the light in it okay so everything
is set up for unity on the all right so you can just simply click to extract it when
you extract it it will give you this folder right here now let's try and drop this inside
our project all right so in the game assets I'm going to try and drop it now if I click
on game assets here it is as you can see this is the lamp right here all right now I'm
going to click on scene view and in here I'm going to add this lamp which near this
pistol okay where we put this pistol so this is the prefab in which I've told you I've fixed the light
and also the materials okay so this is the fixed line print okay you can try and drop it or you
can just try and drop it in the hierarchy in it will be in the same spot right here okay so when
you add it then you can just rotate it to this side closer to the gun okay and then also
let me turn off the gizmos so that we can see okay you can just rotate it a bit like that
and then you can move it up well so now as you can see it looks good okay and also if you want
to increase the light of this you can open it up and in here we have this point light you can
increase its intensity all right but I'm just going to leave this to 1.5 and when you do that
then you can go ahead and play the game that now let's get inside the cabinet see how does it look
all right let's walk there and now as you can see there it is okay
if we look away from it as you can see there is the lamp
all right if we move outside now as you can see from outside it looks good as well okay it provides
the light which we need okay so now the player is for example passing through this cabinet look
towards it the player will be like oh there is a light and when the player gets in there the player
will be able to then see the gun which is right beside it right here and then the player can
pick it up and shoot these on these.